YESHASWANI

Process specialist - Data analyst - TEAM LEADER

About Me

GIS Team leader with 5.6 years of experience in providing GIS analysis and mapping services, and confidential documents, and communicating. Possesses exceptional interpersonal skills, able to work independently and as a part of the team as well.

My Contact

- © 9392231969 /whatsapp:9866127161
- Meerpet, Hyderabad
- # yeshaswanit@gmail.com

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- Problem-Solving Skills
- Presentation Skills.

Education Background

- D.N.R and P.G Engineering College Mater's in computer applications
 Completed in 2015
- Y.S.R and B.S Degree college
 B.sc omputers
 Completed in 2012
- Triveni Degree college MECS Computers

 Completed in 2009
- St. John's public school
 Completed in 2007

Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Telugu
- Punjabi

Professional Experience

Cognizant Technology Solutions Pvt.ltd.

2018 - 2023

Team Lead

2022 - 2023

- Maintained daily tasks to team members to optimise group productivity.
- Fostered positive employees relationships through communication, training and development coaching.
- Collaborated with management team and implement new work procedure and policies Followed staffing strategies to achieve production goals.
- Mentored newly hired employees on operations and implemented training to prevent errors.
- Perform root cause analysis (RCA) on errors and identify policy and workflow apps.
- Created and distributed monthly, quarterly and annual reports to management regarding performance.

Subject Matter Expert

2020-2022

- Organized requirements through gathering/understanding sessions, documenting the requirements and preparing use cases.
- Responded to hundreds of internal inquiries for coaching assistance via the subject matter expert queue, office communicator and email.
- Participated in planning and meetings for Google projects, adding and updating Projects and comments to the process or backlog as needed.
- Mentored newly hired employees on operations and implemented training to prevent errors.
- Performed ad-hoc deep-dive analyses for specific business problems to create, business cases, presentations and reports for senior management.

Senior Process Executive

2019-2020

- Locate potential sites for schools, macro dams, healthcare facilities and roads using spatial analysis.
- Design a standard template to allow for a simplified production process for standardized maps still in use.
- Researched legal descriptions and survey maps to verify property lines and gather requisite information for mapping.
- Gathered, arranged and corrected research data to create representative graphs and charts highlighting results.

Open street maps:

- Create, edit, and maintain OSM data sets to support high quality routing, search, and display use cases.
- Utilization of aerial and street level imagery and other resources to perform job responsibilities
- Research open resources that solve editing tasks and help create new workflows.
- Identify patterns and anomalies in map data and identify corrective actions.

Process Executive

2018-2019

- Review data sets mapped by technicians to ensure quality standards are being met
- Identify error trends and conduct workshops to improve technician and overall project quality.
- Conduct data audits on internal data and external community edits.
- Edit data as necessary.
- Utilize critical thinking to creatively solve problems.
- Report and communicate data issues.